So friends, in this video I am going to tell you
that you can reduce your car's maintenance and
servicing, whatever your question is because
hello hello friends, in my YouTube channel
Star Sports, option Kabir and whenever
you used to insure your Maruti car,
according to the service center,
they have 20 subscribers, as you
can see, I had asked for coupons, if
you wish me luck,
I gave you recharge coupons like
free washing, up message, free
polish, but this is a set of these mangoes, a
turn of free washing, open and there was a
dish which was behind, I will
get a discount on factory portion, celery water,
a
previous song, I cannot do this also, I will do this
later, the
people of those service centers never
say anything that free servicing,
washing, polythene coupons are available,
so while doing your car insurance, you will have to
specifically tell them that give me free
discount coupons, if possible, on the other hand,
give reference of authorized service center to get the
best deal, accused small  This
important information will be useful to you and
by using the steps you will be
able to reduce the maintenance of your car to a great extent.
I have got Africa awards and polishing done through these free coupons. I will
compile the video of it and upload it soon.
Subscribe to this Channel for more
notifications of the sale.